# ANURAG REDDY

248-918-3733

reddyanurag28@gmail.com

Rochester Hills, MI



## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Executive Document Processing Specialist**

#### **Quicken Loans**

m 02/2020 - Ongoing

P Detroit, MI

Leader in Mortgage loan Industry

- Designed and created full document management system and workflows speeding up document production depending on the clients loan type.
- Prepared and presented reports that reflect audit's results and document process

## **Document Review Specialist**

#### **N1 Discovery**

**1** 08/2019 - 12/2019

▼ Troy, MI

Leader in fields of Digital Forensics, eDiscovery, and Cyber Security

- Analyzed confidential documents with important information/details for clients with complex investigations.
- Used Software Program to analyze Digital Forensic documents.

#### ER Scribe

### St. Josephs Hospital

In Scribe Documentation Services

- Documented Patient history on electronic medical records system.
- Worked with many different practitioners and organized patient charts to enhance proper workflow within the emergency department.

#### Sales Associate

#### **Polo Ralph Lauren**

- Established sales expertise and communication skills by enhancing customer service through various promotions within the store.
- Interacted with diverse customers and resolved and disputes/problems with sales and sold variety of products to customers.

## **SKILLS**

Fundamental Knowledge SQL

Basics of SDLC

Fundamental Knowledge html

Microsoft Office Suite

Fundamental Knowledge CSS

**Data Analysis** 

**Agile & Waterfall Terminology** 

**Medical Terminology** 

## PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Highly-motivated, Human Biology Graduate. I am team orientated with exceptional goal setting attributes, time management and organizational skills. I have the ability to effectively multi-task with good communication skills and excellent work ethic and motivation. Have Fundamental knowledge of SQL, html, & Python. B.S. in Human Biology 2013-2017, attended 1 year of Podiatry school. Have a strong desire to learn; proven ability to work on multiple projects at once with strong interpersonal skills.

## **EDUCATION**

## Bachelors of Science in Human **Biology**

**Michigan State University** 

## **STRENGTHS**



#### **Goal Oriented and Motivated**

I work not only until the job is done, but also done right



#### **Team player & Cooperative**

I demonstrate appropriate teamwork to enhance work flow and do my role the best I can



#### **Leadership Skills**

When necessary I direct certain tasks/objectives that must be taken in order to reach goals